Menu

Close

Privacy Policy
==============

1. [Introduction](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#intro)
2. [Information We Collect](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#info-we-collect)
3. [How and Why We May Use Your Information](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#how-we-may-use)
4. [How We May Share Your Information](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#how-we-may-share)
5. [How We Protect Your Information](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#how-we-protect)
6. [Data Retention](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#data-retention)
7. [Rights and Choices You Have with regard to Your Information](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#rights)
8. [Email Sharing](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#emailsharing)
9. [How We Use Tracking Technologies](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#tracking)
10. [International Visitors](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#international)
11. [Information Collection from Children](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#information-collection)
12. [Your California Privacy Rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#california)
13. [Your California Privacy Rights (non-CCPA)](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#california-non)
14. [Changes to Our Privacy Policy](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#changes)
15. [Contact Us](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#contact)

1. **Introduction**. Insticator Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, “Insticator”, “we”, “our” or “us”) want you to be familiar with how we “process” (i.e., collect, store, use and disclose) information. This Privacy Policy only applies to the information processed by Insticator or any third parties acting with our authorization or otherwise provided to us by third parties about you, in each instance, in connection with your (a) interaction with our products and services, including our “Widget” (which generally appears on third-party websites), (b) use of [www.insticator.com](http://www.insticator.com/) and all corresponding domains, subdomains, web pages and websites associated therewith (collectively, the “Sites”) and, (c) use of our mobile, web, tablet, desktop and other applications, including applications made available through Facebook, iOS and Android (collectlvely, the “App(s)”), and (d) use of any other content, applications, features, functionality, information and services offered by us, whether through our Apps, the Sites or otherwise (each of the above individually and collectively referred to herein as the “Services”), and it applies to all individuals, including clients or users of Insticator, who use our products and services (whether offline or online), whether you are accessing and/or using the Services as a registered user or otherwise. This Privacy Policy applies regardless of the device you use to access the Services. Please review our [Terms of Service](http://www.insticator.com/terms), which governs your use of the Services. Any capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning ascribed in the [Terms of Service](http://www.insticator.com/terms). This Privacy Policy will remain in full force and effect, even if your use of the Services or any particular feature or activity offered in connection therewith terminates, expires or is deactivated or suspended for any reason. We will either rely on our legitimate interest or our need to perform under a contract to process your information or you will be asked to affirmatively consent to our processing of your information, all in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not access and/or use the Services or any features, activities, products or services offered through or in connection therewith.
2. **Information We Collect**. We collect information about you when you interact with any of our properties or facilities, visit our Sites and/or Apps, or otherwise use our Services (including our Widget). The information we may process depends upon your interaction with us. The types of personal data that we may process include the following:  
    
    * Registration Information: In order to access and use certain features, portals, content or functions of the Services (e.g., monitoring marketing analytics, viewing Redemption Point status, creating surveys and viewing results, etc.), you may need to register for a “User Account” and provide or make available (e.g., via third party services) to us certain information. When you create a User Account, we will collect personal data as necessary to offer and fulfill the Services you request. Depending on the Services you elect to use, we may ask you to provide your name, email address, mailing address, date of birth, IP address, device identifier, residency information, tax id number and tax information, bank account information and profession or ask that you link your social media account (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, etc.) with our Services. If you choose not to provide some of this information, you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services.
    * Redemption Points Information: If you access or use certain features, portals, content or functions of the Services, including the Widget and accumulate Redemption Points, you may need to provide us with certain information in order for you to use or redeem the Redemption Points. This information includes your name, email address, mailing address, profession and date of birth.
    * Fee-Based Services Information: If you engage in any fee-based Services or other transaction offered on or in connection with the Services, we and/or our third party payment processors may require certain payment information (e.g., credit or debit card number, card type, expiration date and address associated with such credit or debit card) and additional information (e.g. your full name, physical address, employee or employer details, telephone number(s)) to fulfill the applicable services or deliver the applicable products. If you are using Redemption Points to make certain purchases, including in-game purchases, we may require you to provide us with your name, email address, mailing address and profession.
    * Location Information: With your permission, we may process the specific geographic location of your device (e.g., by accessing your device’s GPS and/or using your mobile device ID) to provide you with personalized content within the Services. If you no longer wish to have this location information processed, you can withdraw your consent at any time by disabling the location and/or Bluetooth features in the operating system of your device and/or in the App. If you have any questions about disabling your location and/or Bluetooth features, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
    * Personal Data You Choose to Provide for Marketing or Additional Services: We may process personal data that you choose to provide to us when you elect to participate in optional Site or App features or Services. For example, if you sign up to receive newsletters, marketing emails, promotions or other communications regarding the Services and/or promotions, from us or our preferred third-party products or services providers, or participate in contests, surveys, questionnaires, games and other promotions related to the Services (including the Widget), we may process your name, email address, mailing address, interests, IP address, device identifier, search history, profession and date of birth in order to provide the additional features or Services.
    * Comments, Feedback, Customer Service and Other Inquiries: You have the ability to use the Services to contact us with questions you may have and provide us with comments and or feedback about the Services (e.g., completing a “Contact Us” form on our Sites or surveys relating to our Services) or to communicate with other users of the Services and post comments to or otherwise interact with certain aspects of the Services that are available to the public and/or other users. We will process any information you submit, post or provide in the course of such activities to respond to your comments or feedback. In the event you contact us, we may process information related to conversations, including recording or monitoring customer service calls for quality assurance and training purposes, and to verify your identity.
    * Third Party Platform Information: If you access the Services by logging in using your account credentials from a third-party owned or operated platform/service (e.g., Apple (iTunes, etc.), Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.) (each, a “Third Party Platform”), post content from our Sites, our Apps, and/or our Widget or to a social network, or use various social media features (e.g., “Like” button), we may process certain information from the Third Party Platform, such as your username, “likes”, location, birthday, comments and reviews, direct messages you may send to us, interests, photos, friends, status updates and other information you provided to the Third Party Platform in connection with your account. Depending on your account and privacy settings, we may also be able to see information that you post when using these Third Party Platforms whether or not you are using our Services. The information you post or provide to Third Party Platforms, as well as the controls surrounding these disclosures are governed by the respective policies of these third parties.
    * Information Collected by Tracking Technologies: As further described in [Section 8](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#tracking) of this Privacy Policy and [Cookie Policy](http://www.insticator.com/cookies), when you use the Services and/or third parties may use “cookies” (which are small data files containing information about you that is stored on your device), “embedded scripts”, and other similar tracking technologies (collectively, “Tracking Technologies”) to collect additional information automatically as you interact with the Services. Information collected and processed by our Tracking Technologies will be processed in accordance with our Cookie Policy located [here](http://www.insticator.com/cookies).
    * Advertising Data: We may also use the services of trusted third parties, including advertising networks, social media networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers and marketing analytics service providers to, for example, serve you advertisements on the Services or while using other websites, populate user-specific advertisements and/or measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on or in connection with the Services (“Third Party Advertising Providers”). Third Party Advertising Providers enable us to provide you with more useful advertisements about our Services or the services of third parties which are tailored specifically to your interests or to individuals with similar characteristics to our customers and users, including by using tools like Google’s [“Customer Match”](https://support.google.com/google-ads/answer/6379332?hl=en) or Facebook [“Custom Audiences”](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/341425252616329). These tools combine information you have provided to us through your use of our Services with other data processed about you through third-party sites, permitting you to view personalized advertisements about Insticator or our third party partners on other websites you browse or when you are searching for similar products or services. Additionally, we may use platform tools like Facebook’s [“Lookalike Audiences”](https://www.facebook.com/business/help/465262276878947) to share information you have provided us with social media sites to create “lookalike audiences” (i.e., users with similar characteristics to our customers or like-minded consumers) and provide such users with tailored advertisements about Insticator or our third party partners. When we use these tools, you can withdraw your consent to this use of your personal data at any time by emailing us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) . Third Party Advertising Providers may use their own cookies and other tracking technologies. Insticator does not control these Third Party Advertising Providers and/or their use of cookies, which is instead governed by the privacy policies and/or cookie policies of any such Third Party Advertising Provider.
    * Browsing Information, Logs, Usage Data and Other Device Information: When you visit our Sites and Apps and use our Widget, we may process information about your activities on third-party websites and our Sites, Apps and Widget through the use of Tracking Technologies, as further explained in Sections [8](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#tracking) below and our [Cookie Policy](http://www.insticator.com/cookies). Providing this information is not mandatory, and cookies can be disabled by visiting or Cookie Management Tool located [here](https://www.onetrust.com/). However, please note that our Sites and Widget may not offer the same functionalities when certain cookies are disabled.
3. **How and Why We May Use Your Information**. We may process your personal data (depending on your interaction with us) for any reason that is permitted under data protection laws in accordance with this Privacy Policy, which may include the purposes below. Note that the legal bases outlined below are required to be included under European Union (“EU”) data protection laws, but are not required to be included if you do not reside in the EU.
    
    1. * To fulfill our contractual obligations under an existing agreement with you to provide you with products and services you requested, or in anticipation of entering into such an agreement with you, including, without limitation:
            * To provide or fulfill any services, orders or products that you request or purchase in connection with the Services including for accounting, auditing or other internal functions, and to offer you an overview of your transactional history;
            * To enable you to collect, use and redeem Redemption Points;
            * To communicate with you about your account, transactions, applications and the Services;
            * To respond to requests for information and services, including services from a third party;
            * To manage, evaluate and administer your User Account, including sending you information about your account status and provide you with information and statics about your use of the Services;
            * To manage and administer your business accounts, including sending you transaction-related emails for such things as account verification, purchase and billing confirmation;
            * To enforce your legal rights under an agreement; and
            * To provide you with an estimate for our products or services.
        * To pursue our legitimate business interests, including, without limitation:
            * To provide you with a more personalized level of service, including information and services related to the products and services you purchase from us or that may be available from a trusted third party;
            * To manage our business needs, such as monitoring, analyzing, modifying and improving our Services’, including the Sites’, Apps’ and Widget’s, functionality and performance, including changes/updates to features of the Sites/Apps/Widget, technical and security notices;
            * For the security and safety of our users, clients, publishers, advertisers and visitors, and for purposes of fraud prevention, including preventing fraud and abuse on and unauthorized access to the Services, Sites, Apps and Widget;
            * To provide you with information about products and services you have purchased or indicated your interest in;
            * To determine which features and functionality of the Services users like best to help us operate, enhance and improve the Services, including by asking you to participate in a survey relating your use of the Services;
            * To provide you with information about how the Services work and interact with the services of our third party partners;
            * To respond to any customer service requests, such as resolving your problems or responding to your questions, managing any complaints or feedback you provide;
            * For statistical analysis of aggregated data to help us segment our offerings and develop our Services;
            * To better understand the way in which our Sites, Apps and Widget are working and offer you a better user experience, to create statistics in relation to the use of our Sites, Apps, Widget and our Services generally;
            * To help us diagnose technical issues and problems related to our Services;
            * To grow our business, including our products and services;
            * To get to know our potential and existing users, publishers, advertisers, clients, consumers, and users; and
            * To identify relevant content shared with potential and current users.
        * To comply with our regulatory and legal obligations or to enforce our legal rights, including, without limitation:
            * To meet reporting requirements (e.g., filing tax forms);
            * To retain documents and information related to a legal action;
            * To enforce the Terms of Service; and
            * To report data breaches or unauthorized access to the Services.
        * With your consent\*, including, without limitation:
            * To provide location-specific functionality, features, services or offers;
            * To market to you by delivering marketing materials about Insticator’s and our third party partners’ products and services, as well as the products and services of unaffiliated third party businesses;
            * To display online advertising and marketing information based on your use of the Services, including interaction with the Widget, and other websites services and platforms that you have visited;
            * To provide you with tailored advertisements about Insticator or our third party partners on third-party websites, we may provide your personal data to Third Party Advertising Providers that combine such data with information collected by third-parties to send you advertisements on our Sites, Apps and Widget, and third-party websites and other digital properties, about our exclusive offers, news and products or services tailored to you and your interests;
            * To provide personalized services offered by us or third-party partners on third-party websites and other digital properties and online services;
            * To enable you to connect with others who use our Services; and
            * For other purposes for which you may grant consent.
    
    \*You can withdraw your consent at any time by following the steps in [Section 8](http://www.insticator.com/privacy#tracking) of this Privacy Policy.
    
4. **How We May Share Your Information**. In connection with our global operations, we may share information we collect from you or about you with some of our affiliates, publishers, third party partners and third party service providers as necessary to assist us in providing the Services to you, as set forth in more detail below:  
    
    1. * Our Group Entities: We may disclose your personal data to our group entities that are affiliates and/or subsidiaries of Insticator in order to provide you with tailored products, services and communications.
        * Publishers, Clients and Third-Party Partners: We may disclose your personal data to publishers, clients and third party partners in connection with the Services, including with respect to your interaction with the Widget embedded in the websites of publishers, clients and third party partners, to share information about your interaction with the Widget and publishers’ websites, to provide you with Services you request and to enable a publisher or third party partner to provide you with information about their service and/or product offerings. Please note that if you visit a website operated by a publisher or third party partner, any personal data you provide through that website will be subject to the privacy policy of that third party and not to this Privacy Policy.
        * Service Providers: We may partner with other companies to help us operate certain aspects of our businesses, including the hosting of our Sites and Apps, operation of our technology infrastructure, processing of payments and redemption of Redemption Points, and fulfillment of certain services or products you request from us. We carefully select such third party operators, merchants, website hosts, service providers and participants to your transactions for the purpose of (1) assisting with facilitating transactions on or through the Services, (2) providing information technology and customer service assistance, and (3) providing, offering, supporting, administering, maintaining and enabling the Services (including providing a full range of content, services, features and functions offered on or in connection with the Services).
        * Advertising Providers: In order to provide you with marketing and exclusive offers, including emails and advertisements tailored to you and your interests on and off the Services, we may provide your information to Third Party Advertising Providers.
        * Co-Sponsors of Promotions: From time to time, we may co-sponsor promotions, sweepstakes, prize draws, competitions or contests with other companies. If you enter one of these sweepstakes or contests, we may share your information with the co-sponsor or third-party sponsor.
        * Corporate Transactions or Events: We may disclose your personal data in connection with a merger, sale of substantially all of our assets or stock, joint venture, transfer, corporate reorganization or other disposition of our business.
        * Pursuant to Law, Rule or Regulation: We may share or disclose your information with other parties as we deem necessary or appropriate under applicable law, rule or regulation. Examples of these purposes include: to respond to requests from public, governmental and regulatory authorities, to comply with court orders, to obtain legal remedies or limit our damages, to enforce this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use, and to protect the rights, safety and/or property of you, our employees or others.
        * To Fulfill Your Requests: If you elect to use certain authentication or sharing features available on the Sites or via the Services, we may use your personal data to fulfill your request to share content with or provide access to such third parties (e.g. Facebook, LinkedIn, or Twitter).
        * Additional Non-Personal Information: We may share aggregated and/or anonymized data, meaning data that cannot identify you personally, that includes information we collect through your interaction with the Services. We may share this information with our publishers, clients and third party partners in order to improve the Services and their services and to better understand your interaction with the Widget, the Services and their products and services.
    
    With regard to our third party service providers, we only provide such third parties with access to your information to the extent reasonably necessary for them to provide the services for which they are contractually engaged to provide. We request that all of our service providers maintain commercially reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and must agree to keep such information secure and confidential in line with this Privacy Policy.
    
5. **How We Protect Your Information.** While no data transmission over the internet or wireless networks is 100% secure from intrusion, we maintain and have implemented reasonable physical, electronic, technical and procedural security policies and measures to protect the personal data that we process, which are consistent with applicable privacy and security laws. These policies and measures are designed to prevent against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, modification and disclosure and unlawful destruction of your personal data. The security measures can change and be modified over time, but generally include, but are not limited to, firewalls, data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, servers and hardware and information access authorization controls and regular testing and updating of the systems. While we are dedicated to securing your personal data and our systems and Services, you are responsible for securing and maintaining the privacy of your credentials (e.g., user name, password or account information) and verifying that personal data we maintain about you is accurate and current. It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate information, and to keep such information up to date. We cannot and will not be responsible for any problems or liability that may arise if you do not give us accurate, truthful or complete information, or you fail to update such information. We will reject and delete any entry that we believe in good faith to be false, fraudulent or inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
6. **Data Retention**. We access, retain, store and use personal data for the least amount of time necessary pursuant to our relationship with you (e.g., to provide you with or access to our products and services), in accordance with our data retention policies and applicable law. We do not process more personal data than is necessary to fulfill our obligations to you or at law or for purposes stated in this Privacy Policy
7. **Rights and Choices You Have with regard to Your Information**. If you are an EU citizen or reside in the EU, you may have certain additional rights with respect to the personal data you provided to us. To the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws, under EU laws you may:
    * Access or modify your personal data;
    * Object, on grounds relating to your particular situation, at any time to the processing of your personal data if the legal ground we are relying on is our legitimate interest or in the public interest;
    * Request that your personal data be erased if it is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was processed, you have withdrawn consent to, or object to, the processing of such personal data and we meet no other legitimate basis for such processing or it has been unlawfully processed;
    * Restrict the processing of your personal data if you contest its accuracy or the lawfulness of our processing, we no longer need it but you need it for a legal claim or you have objected to its processing and await verification of our legitimate grounds for processing it;
    * Stop receiving our marketing communications. If you opt out of marketing emails, you will continue to receive messages from us about your relationship with us where permitted by law;
    * Under certain circumstances, have your personal data transferred to another company; and
    * Withdraw any consents that you have previously provided to allow us to process your personal data.
        
        If you wish to exercise any of these rights please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Although we urge you to contact us to find a solution for every concern you may have, you always have the right to lodge a complaint with your competent data protection authority. Please note that some requests may require you to verify your identity.
        
        Modifying Privacy Settings: You also may be able to adjust certain privacy, permission and user account settings by sending an “unsubscribe” email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), responding to request alerts or notifications on your device or by navigating to the settings, account or privacy section (as the case may be) of your device or the applicable Third Party Platform and limiting certain Service functionality (e.g., location services, etc.). Please be aware that if you limit the collection of certain information, you may not be able to use all of the features and functionality of the Services.
        
8. **Email Sharing.** When you use our Commenting Unit, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email, IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our identity partners/service providers and/or publishing partners. Online identification codes are created that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online, in-app, and cross-channel advertising, and it may be shared with advertising companies and our publishing partners to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. Our publishing partners may also use these email addresses to subscribe you to their email newsletters which you may opt out of.
9. **Withdrawing Consent; How We Use Tracking Technologies.** When you visit our Sites and Apps, use our Services (including the Widget), or visit a third-party website for which we provide online services, we and our publishers, third party partners and vendors may use Tracking Technologies to recognize you as a repeat visitor, authenticate your usage and/or device, keep track of your preferences, visits and Redemption Points and to customize your online experiences, the Services you use, and other online content and advertising, measure the effectiveness of promotions and perform analytics, and to mitigate risk, prevent potential fraud, and promote trust and safety across the Sites, the Apps and the Services. Certain aspects and features of our Services and Sites are only available through the use of Tracking Technologies, so if you choose to disable or decline Tracking Technologies, your use of the Sites, Apps and Services may be limited or not possible. Please review our Cookie Policy [here](http://www.insticator.com/cookies) to learn more about how we use and how you may adjust and disable Tracking Technologies. If you wish to receive more information about our privacy practices or to withdraw your consent to Insticator’s use of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
10. **International Visitors.** Our operations are supported by a network of computers, cloud-based servers, and other infrastructure and information technology, including, but not limited to, third-party service providers. We and some of our subsidiaries and affiliates, servers, publishers, partners, vendors and service providers may not be located in your jurisdiction and may also be located outside of the European Economic Area and Switzerland. If you are an EU citizen or resident in the EU, we will transfer your personal data to the United States or Ukraine in accordance with EU data protection law requirements by using model contractual clauses that have been approved by the European Commission or other appropriate means. Please note that such transfers may also be necessary in order to perform our obligations under a contract with you, to fulfill a request made by you, to meet a legal or regulatory obligation and/or through obtaining you express consent. If you make transactions with parties outside the EEA or Switzerland or connect our Service with platforms, such as Facebook, outside the EEA or Switzerland, we are required to transfer your Personal Data with those parties in order to provide the requested Service to you. If you wish to gain more information about such transfers, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
11. **Information Collection from Children**. Our Sites, Apps, Widget and Services are not directed to children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect information, including personal information, from children or other individuals who are not legally able to use our Sites, Apps, Widget and/or Services. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information from an individual under the age listed above, we will promptly delete it, unless we are legally obligated to retain such data. If you believe that we have mistakenly or unintentionally collected information from someone under the applicable age listed above, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). For users in the United States, please also visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website [here](http://www.ftc.gov/) for information about protecting children’s privacy online.
12. **Your California Privacy Rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA).**If you are an individual who is a resident of California (a California “consumer”), you have the following rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act, which went into effect on January 1, 2020, with respect to your “personal information” (as defined by CCPA):
    
    * **Right to Know.**  You have the right to request that we disclose to you, following your “verifiable consumer request”:
        * The categories of personal information we have collected about you
        * The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected
        * The business or commercial purpose for collecting personal information
        * The categories of third parties with which we share personal information
        * The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you
        * With respect to our sales of your personal information:
            * The categories of personal information that we sold about you
            * The categories of third parties to which your personal information was sold, by category or categories of personal information for each category of third parties to which the personal information was sold
            * The business or commercial purpose for selling personal information
        * The categories of personal information about you that we disclosed for a business purpose
    
    * **Right to Delete.**  You have the right to request that we delete, following your “verifiable consumer request”, the specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
        * Categories of personal information we collect
        * Specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you
        * Categories of sources from which we collect personal information
    
    * **Right to Opt-Out.**  You have the right, at any time, to direct us not to sell your personal information. To exercise your “right to opt-out” by clicking the link below:

    [DO NOT SELL MY PERSONAL INFORMATION](https://www.insticator.com/5565-2/).
    
    * **Right to Non-Discrimination.**  We may not discriminate against you because you exercise any of your rights under CCPA, including by:
        * Denying goods or services to you
        * Charging you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties
        * Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to you
        * Suggesting that you will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services
    
    Methods of Submitting Requests to Exercise the “Right to Know” or the “Right to Delete”
    
    If you are a California consumer, you may submit requests to exercise your “right to know” or your “right to delete” via either of the following methods:
    
    * **By email**, to: [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    * **Via our interactive webform**, available [here](https://www.insticator.com/5565-2/)
        
        CCPA Personal Information
        
        We collect (and during the last 12 months have collected) the following categories of personal information, from the following categories of sources, and for the following business or commercial purpose:
        
    * **Identifiers** (such as a real name, postal address, email address, an online identifier, or an internet protocol address)
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion) and/or from third-party vendors (such as vendors that use cookies and other online tracking technologies on our Sites, Apps, Widget, and in third-party services, and third-party data providers)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including:
                        * Providing or fulfilling services, orders or products requested or purchased in connection with the Services
                        * Enabling consumers to collect, use and redeem Redemption Points
                        * Communicating with consumers about their accounts, transactions, applications and the Services
                        * Providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
                    * Monitoring, analyzing, modifying and improving our Services, Sites, Apps, and Widget, including their functionality and performance and for security and fraud prevention
    * **Characteristics of Protected Classifications** (such as race, religion, and sexual orientation)
        
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion) and/or from third-party vendors (such as third-party data providers)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third party partners in connection with such parties’ marketing and advertising activities
    * **Commercial information** (such as purchasing history in connection with, for example, home ownership and automobile ownership)
        
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
    * **Internet or other electronic network activity information** (such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding interactions with our Sites, Apps, Widget, and advertising)
        
        * We receive such information from third-party vendors, including ad platforms and vendors that use cookies and other online tracking technologies on our Sites, Apps, and Widget, and in third-party services (including in emails and advertisements)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including:
                        * Providing or fulfilling services, orders or products requested or purchased in connection with the Services
                        * Providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
                    * Monitoring, analyzing, modifying and improving our Services, Sites, Apps, and Widget, including their functionality and performance and for security and fraud prevention  
                        
    * **Geolocation data**
        
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion) and/or from third-party vendors (such as vendors that use cookies and other online tracking technologies on our Sites, Apps, and Widget, and in third-party services, and third-party data providers)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including:
                        * Providing or fulfilling services, orders or products requested or purchased in connection with the Services
                        * Providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
                    * Monitoring, analyzing, modifying and improving our Services, Sites, Apps, and Widget, including their functionality and performance and for security and fraud prevention
    * **Professional or employment-related information** (such as job title or industry)
        
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion) and/or from third-party vendors (such as third-party data providers)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
    * **Education information** (such as highest level of education completed)
        
        * We receive such information directly from consumers (such as when they provide information in connection with a contest, survey, questionnaire, game or other promotion) and/or from third-party vendors (such as third-party data providers)
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)
    * **Inferences** (drawn from any of the other categories of personal information of the information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting, for example, a consumer’s product preferences)
        
        * We receive such information from third-party vendors, including vendors that perform analytics and remarketing services for us
            
            * For our operational and commercial purposes, including:
                
                * * Managing, performing, and administering our contracts and relationships with consumers, including providing consumers with more personalized services and information about products and services offered by us or third parties
                    * Marketing and advertising, including in connection with the provision of advertisements tailored to consumers’ interests
                    * Selling of consumers’ personal information, including to publishers, clients and third-party partners in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities)  

    Disclosure of Personal Information for a Business Purpose
    
    We disclose (and during the last 12 months have disclosed) each of the categories of personal information set forth in the table above (i.e., identifiers, protected classifications, commercial information, Internet or other electronic network activity information, geolocation data, and inferences/profiles) for a business purpose with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf, including data analytics providers, technology service providers, customer service providers, and advertising and marketing service providers and platforms. These services may include performing business and sales analysis, supporting the functionality of our Sites, Apps and Widget and supporting other features offered through our Sites, Apps and/or Widget, providing customer service, and providing advertising and marketing services (including delivering tailored advertising and email marketing campaigns, and analyzing and improving the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing).
    
    Sale of Personal Information
    
    We sell (and during the last 12 months have sold) each of the categories of personal information set forth in the table above (i.e., identifiers, protected classifications, commercial information, Internet or other electronic network activity information, geolocation data, and inferences/profiles) to publishers, clients and third-party partners, including in connection with such parties’ operational and commercial activities (including marketing and advertising activities). As of January 1, 2020, we do not sell the personal information of California consumers under the age of 16 without affirmative authorization.
    
13.  **Your California Privacy Rights (non-CCPA)**. If you are a resident of the State of California, in addition to the rights and information set forth in Section 11 above with respect to CCPA, you have the right to obtain certain information about the types of “personal information” (as defined by California’s “Shine the Light” law) that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. To request a list of companies, if any, to which we have provided personal information for our own marketing purposes, please submit your request [via this form](https://www.insticator.com/5565-2/) or by postal mail to Insticator Inc., c/o Privacy Administrator, 2 Park Avenue, 10th Floor, New York, New York, 10016, Attn: Your California Shine the Light Privacy Rights. All requests must be labeled “Your California Shine the Light Privacy Rights” on the email subject line or envelope or post card. For all requests, please clearly state that the request is related to “Your California Privacy Rights”, include your name, street address, city, state, zip code and e-mail address (your street address is optional if you wish to receive a response to your request via email) and indicate your preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information. You can always opt-out or unsubscribe by emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by [filling out this form](https://www.insticator.com/5565-2/).
    
    California law also requires us to disclose how we respond to browser “Do Not Track” signals. We have not yet developed a response to “Do Not Track” signals sent by browsers, and do not change any of our data collection practices when we receive such signals. We will continue to evaluate potential responses to “Do Not Track” signals in light of industry developments or legal changes.
    
14. **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**. From time to time, we may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives, third party requirements or changes in the law, technology, our information processing practices or the features and functionality of the Services, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting. When we change this Privacy Policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our Sites along with the updated Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Services after we post a revised Privacy Policy (and, where appropriate, notify you of same) signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. We may continue to process your information based on our legitimate interests or in order to fulfill our obligations under a contract and/or may also seek your affirmative consent to the terms of the updated Privacy Policy. For example, we may ask for your consent before implementing new uses of the personal data that we’ve already collected from you based on such consent, if such new use was not addressed by the privacy policy under which such information was collected or if our legal basis for processing such information changes. The Services (including the Widget) may be linked to, rely on and/or be integrated with websites, applications, interfaces, services and/or platforms operated by third-party companies, including service providers and Third Party Platforms. The Services may also feature advertisements from other third parties. Insticator is not responsible for the privacy practices of any websites, applications, interfaces, services and platforms operated by such third parties that are linked to, rely on and/or integrated with the Services, or for the privacy practices of third party advertising companies. Once you leave the Services via such a link, access a third party application, interface, service, or platform, including Third Party Platforms and websites operated by service providers or third parties, or click on or navigate to an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of such third party to determine, among other things, how they will handle any information that they may collect from you.
15. **Contact Us.** In addition to the contact methods set forth above with respect to particular requests you may have, if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, how we handle your personal data or any of the terms or conditions of this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at the addresses set forth below: By Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.insticator.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)OR
    
    By Mail:
    
    Insticator, Inc.  
    Attn: Privacy Matters  
    382 NE 191st Street  
    PMB 63665  
    Miami, FL 33179-3899

Let’s talk about what our suite of engagement and monetization solutions can do for you

Socials

Our Products

Advertisers

* 

About

Notice to California Consumers. Insticator may collect “Identifiers,” “Characteristics of protected classifications,” “Commercial information,” “Internet or other electronic network activity,” “Geolocation data,” “Professional or employment-related information,” and/or “Education information” when you visit this website, and may use such information to draw inferences and for other operational and commercial purposes (including the sale of such information). For more information, please see our [Privacy Policy…](https://www.insticator.com/privacy/)

This website uses cookies to improve your experience. You can opt-out if you wish.  
  
Cookie settingsRejectAccept

Cookie Policy

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how this website is used. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.

Non-necessary

 Non-necessary

Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.

SAVE & ACCEPT
